

## SUMMARY

Front End Developer who is passionate about building world class web applications. Over 10 years of experience in web design and interactive multimedia development with digital marketing companies. Bright, talented, ambitious and self-motivated.



778-996-9209



inok.lim@hotmail.com



www.linkedin.com/in/inoklim



inok-lim.github.io

# **EXPERIENCE**



#### Web Developer

Sage, Richmond | Mar 2015 - Rresent

- Front End Developer responsible for web application development and creative cloud engineering.
- · Wireframe, code and review more than 300 web screens.
- Drive and guide best practice implementation of HTML/CSS framework for multiple development teams.
- Boosted user experience scores and NPS by 60% over company-wide previous best through UI optimization and modernization project.



#### **Graphic Designer**

Museum, NRC, etc.

Skyblace Communications, Ottawa I Jan 2004 – Jul 2005

• Developed more than 20 e-Learning and interactive multimedia

projects and apps in Flash and HTML Clients including

Starbucks, Burger King, Health Canada, Canadian War

• Responsible for the design and execution of all brand promotion materials to attract and maintain advertising such as: event web site, brochures, publications, logo designs, newsletters, invitations, conference multi-media kits.



#### **Production Designer**

Best Buy Canada, Burnaby | Aug 2014 - Jan 2015

- · Designed multiple weekly eNewsletters in bi-lingual.
- Developed interactive banners (in Flash, HTML5 and CSS3)
- · Produced digital marketing signage, brochures and flyers.



**Interactive Multimedia Designer** 

SIGPRO Wireless Inc., Ottawa I Sep 2001 - Dec 2003

- · Designed and produced marketing and sales promotion materials such as: logos, corporate stationary, product sheets, newsletters, product package designs, sales presentations, tradeshow ads, invitations, media kits, seasonal content specials and company brochures.
- · Worked with marketing team organizing trade shows and conferences including WIC2001 to WIC2003.
- Presented Award of Appreciation in April 2002 for supporting the company for the event project: Wireless Industry Congress 2001 & CTIA Wireless 2002, and Award of Excellence for hard work and contribution to the company in November 2002.



## Web Designer / Multimedia Developer

Pixelera Inc., Ottawa I Aug 2005 - Jun 2013

- Energetic Adobe certified expert web designer with +10 years of experience.
- Designed average of 5 website per month.
- Prototyped/templated new designs into HTML

## **EDUCATION**

## Algonquin College of Applied Arts and Technology

Post-Diploma, Interactive Multimedia, 2001

#### **Hanyang University**

Bachelor's Degree, Educational/Instructional Technology, 1997

## **SKILLS**



HTML5, CSS3, LESS/SASS, JavaScript, jQuery, AngularJS



Bootstrap, npm, Node.is, React, Kendo UI ASP.NET, Razor, MVC, AJAX, JSON, XML

